Let us prepare for Prince Zardos' arrival.
My dear General, what do you have to say
to me, Draco?
Our army is ready to fight.
Zandra.
I do not expect anything from us,
especially from the Terra Earth army.
Zul, everything is ready, Prince Zardos.
We are just waiting for your order.
My order is to surrender the planet Terra
Earth.
They're here.
Captain, Mr. O'Planet, are you alert?
The Bosanians have arrived.
Aye, sir.
Sir, all stations report ready.
Attention, all nations of the Earth
Defense Forces.
This is your Supreme Commander,
General Robinson, speaking.
We have confirmed that a large alien force
has entered the Earth's atmosphere.
All international sectors must immediately
implement all defense protocols.
May God save us all.
The whole world is doing everything to
defend our planet.
But we are no match to these invaders,
sir.
Also, we are receiving a report that
aliens are spreading all around the globe.
Sir, there's fear and chaos everywhere.
I'm afraid that these aliens might succeed
in invading us if we don't stop them.
We have no hope if it's not our last line
of defense, the Voltis V.
Jamie Robinson, return to base.
Roger that.
Little John Armstrong, return to base.
Yes, sir.
Big Bird Armstrong, return to base.
Mark Gordon, return to base.
Steve Armstrong, return to base.
On the way.
Red alert.
All crew to battle station.
Ma, what's going on?
Why do you know everything about the camp?
Maybe it's on a need-to-know basis.
At least I don't have a mother who works
here.
But them?
They're your family.
The least you could do is tell them what
all this training is for.
I guess there's no more reason for me to
keep the truth from all of you.
Observe.
The world is under attack by an alien
menace.
And you...
will save the world.
Our world.
Aliens?
Did I hear that right?
What you told us before is true,
Dr. Smith.
I thought it was a joke.
We'll save the world from these aliens.
So you're saying we're in the middle of an
interplanetary war?
Ma, this is the truth.
Yes, Steve.
This is the reason why you're mothers.
That's why we made a Voltess robot.
Because we've known for a long time that
these alien invaders are coming.
So you better suit up.
The Volt machines are ready for you.
Go.
Now.
The aliens have arrived.
They are vicious and heartless.
They have caused major destruction all
over the globe.
You must defeat and destroy them.
All the military forces of the world are
waiting for you.
Voltess team, you are the last line of
defense.
The whole world will be in danger if this
happens.
And this will be the end of humankind.
This cannot happen.
Do everything you can to save our planet.
Everyone, to your battle stations.
Kids, take care.
Be good.
Be brave.
Be...
Be safe.
Yes, Ma.
Mark, Jamie, take care.
Little John.
Marianne, we're running out of time.
Let's go.
Mark, you're number two.
Steve, you're number one.
Okay.
Big Bert, number three.
Okay, Ma.
Little John, number four.
Roger.
Jamie, five.
Launch conveyors, now.
Attention, all machines.
Excuse me, we don't have all the controls
here yet.
Can you give us like five minutes?
The controls of that is similar to the
flight simulator.
Steve, what else?
It's all just the same.
Steve, take command.
Mark.
Big Bert, you handle weaponry and
armaments.
Jamie, medical and communication.
Little John.
Do what you do best.
Engineering.
Copy that, best friend.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
Launch.
Ah!
Easy, boy, easy.
Mark.
That's not a horse.
Little John, are you okay?
Huh?
Wait, how did you know?
Jamie.
Guys, do you see the weapons list?
The weapons list?
Fort, bazooka, chain knuckles.
Oh, ultra electromagnetic whip.
Big Bert, did you just say whip?
Yeehaw!
Let's go get the million.
Guys, guys, guys, get your head in the
game.
What is the medical condition of the team?
Captain Fowler reporting all five biosigns
of all team members are okay.
Holy.
There's a lot of them.
Wow.
Lin, wow.
Lim, can we handle these guys?
It's too late.
We won't make it.
Lim, don't be afraid.
Remember, the whole world is counting on
us.
Brother is right.
There's no time to lose.
Let's go.
Little John, please.
Don't mess up again, okay?
I'll follow you, okay?
Yes, brother.
Mama, don't worry.
Of course, I'll worry.
You don't have enough training.
Mama, I can do this.
This is just a video game.
What video game?
Oh, my God.
Team,
let's engage.
Commit, commit.
Use your weapons.
Most of the controls are voice activated.
Oh, cool.
Helm boomerang.
Frigate rocket.
Ranger missile.
Bomber missile.
Lander shuriken.
There's no end to the weapons of this
planet.
This day will not end.
And we will destroy them.
Let's not be reckless.
We will not be defeated by war.
You're crazy, Draco.
They don't have a chance against our army.
There's still a lack of hard work.
I want to see everyone on that planet die.
What is that?
Take out our weapons.
Take out Doc O'Gaga.
Do you want to be free, John Frey?
Watch how the Terrans will be defeated in
our battle.
Sir, we are detecting an alien signature.
This is the first time we've picked up a
signal like this.
On screen.
Sir, enemy classification.
It's a Bosnian beast fighter.
Send me the coordinates of that beast
fighter.
Now!
Yes, sir.
Beast fighter?
That's a beautiful name for our army.
Draco, continue your promise.
They will only live longer if they can't
open our weapons.
Sir, new energy signature detected.
Computer identifies it as a beast fighter.
Bolstein, the Bosnians have released a
beast fighter.
Beast fighter?
What is that?
Kaiju!
Evasive maneuvers!
Now is your better chance to bolt in.
We're going to bolt in the robot?
What do we do, Doc?
Bolt in, team.
You need to fly in a V formation.
Steve, your cruiser should be in the front
and center.
From now on, this will be your V
formation.
Copy?
Copy, Ma'am.
Team, let's V together.
V formation now!
Now, you will see a red button next to
your center console.
To activate the robot transformation,
push that to start the bolt-in sequence.
Roger that.
Let's bolt in!
We're almost there.
Let's get our legs together.
We believe in each other.
We're all in this together.
We're almost there.
We're almost
there.
Geoffrey, look at this.
These Terra Ertl soldiers are
extraordinary.
You lack discipline.
I'm sure they will not defeat Doc O'Gaga.
Draco, let the battle begin.
Now, Geoffrey.
That's their champion.
If that's their champion, I'm sure they
will defeat our soldier.
What do they call him?
Our beast fighter.
The Terra Ertl soldiers are extraordinary.
Draco.
Doc O'Gaga, make sure Doc O'Gaga will not
defeat their champion.
Yes, sir.
What do they call him?
Our champion.
Don't worry, Little John.
We have trained for this, remember?
Yes, we have trained, but Little John is
not.
We'll be in trouble if something happens
to him.
Nothing bad will happen to me.
Trust me.
Be strong.
Remember, the whole world is in our hands.
That's why we have to win.
Roger.
Draco, I'm getting hot.
Finish him.
Now, Geoffrey.
Ah!
Big Bert!
Bio warning signs.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Oh,
no.
He's strong.
Everyone's bio signs are good.
Little John, are you okay?
I'm okay.
I just slipped.
Let's get him back.
Weapon recommendation, chain knuckles.
Roger.
Chain knuckles!
This is an ultra-electromagnetic weapon.
Mark, that's your specialty.
You can do it.
Ultra-electromagnetic weapon!
Ultra-electromagnetic staff!
Yes!
Oh, nice.
Wait.
Why do I feel like we're losing?
Shut up, Zul.
No.
Let's finish this.
Shut up, laser sword.
Shut up.
Shut up!
Yay!
I can't believe it.
They lost to Doku Gaga.
John.
You are a brave warrior.
You may have the advantage now,
Ertugrul.
But the fight is not over yet.
There is no planet that can defeat the
mighty Empire of Buzot.
Sir!
Team Voltus V reporting.
Welcome back.
Mission accomplished.
Job well done, Team Voltus V.
We are so proud of you.
And your parents are waiting for hugs.
Aris!
Prove yourself.
You made me.
Thank you.
Your father will be so proud of you.
Good job.
Thank you, Dad.
Mark.
You did a great job.
You made me proud of you.
Thank you.
John Frey.
Zardoz.
What's the news on Terra Air 2?
I was hoping it would fall into your
hands.
I am sorry.
But we are on the same side.
They have a strong army.
Which means?
Your army was defeated.
I thought you were good.
I thought you were one of the heroes since
you defeated your father.
Aren't you ashamed of my ministers?
Of the people of Busan who idolize you.
Where is your talent?
Your intelligence?
Your courage?
Why were you defeated?
Forgive me, John Frey.
I promise you.
I will not go back to Busan.
Until the planet Terra Air 2 is destroyed.
Yes.
Don't come back until you can't do
anything for me.
Don't embarrass me, Zardoz.
Don't embarrass yourself like your father,
Sirotgar.
Don't embarrass the whole of Busan.
Najmi Imperium.
Dad.
Mom.
We know you are angry.
You are afraid.
Especially little John.
You are three, son.
What if you were defeated?
Then all three of you will be gone from
me.
But what happened is not what you are
afraid of, Mom.
Mom.
Trust.
We trust you.
You, Papa.
Dr. Smith.
That's why we have the confidence to fight
using the Voltis robot.
Because we know what you did.
Trust, Mom.
That's why, Mom.
Mom, you should trust your father's
creations.
And you should trust your children.
Yes, Mom.
That's why you should let me go.
Because we need the whole world.
We are your gift to our planet.
Be careful, children.
Don't let anything bad happen to you.
Promise.
I can't believe that we were defeated by
the Terra Air 2 because of the Voltis 5.
Don't worry.
I'm studying about their main weapon.
Draco.
What are you investigating?
I'm just wondering how the Terra Air 2 got
this technology from the Voltis 5.
I'm sure that it's not from their planet.
Is there a way to find out where the
Terras hide their weapons?
That's what the Minister wants to know.
Let's just wait for his surprise.
Wait.
Can't we know everything?
Why is Zul here?
Zul.
What do you want?
Next time, dear Prince.
Why is it dark here?
Surprise!
Thank you, but it's my birthday tomorrow.
What's going on, Mom?
You seem to be in a hurry.
And if we're going to do everything
tomorrow, then it's not a surprise
anymore.
Don't call it a surprise.
Blow your candle.
One, two, wish.
Wish first.
Well, I want all of us to blow the candle.
I want to share my birthday luck with all
of you.
Go ahead.
One, two, three.
What's your wish?
Well, I don't have a wish for myself
anymore.
So, my wish is that you are always safe.
And that your wishes will come true.
You know what I always say.
Be strong, be brave, be safe.
So, it means that my wish will come true.
You know, I have a wish too.
Really, son?
You have a crush on Jamie?
These are all fake news.
Don't believe them.
Mom is just stressed.
Hey, that's enough.
You might get into a fight.
Steve, you're the older brother.
You shouldn't hurt your siblings.
Yes, ma'am.
And you two, don't tease your siblings too
much.
Let's eat.
Let's eat this.
Hurry up.
Okay,
one, two, three.
How big is Big Bird?
Half of it is Big Bird.
Zul!
Where is Voltes Five?
You've been looking for him since
yesterday.
I'm getting hot.
What's going on?
Principal Sandoz, this is what I want to
show you.
I've been told that there's a strong
energy coming from that island.
There's a strong signal that the defense
of Terra Ertube is in danger.
Voltes Five is probably hiding there.
Terra Ertube people are smart.
They put their camp on a hidden island.
But they haven't been able to hide from
us.
When are you going to attack, Jomfre?
We're just waiting for your budget.
Is our Beast Fighter ready?
He's ready, Jomfre.
I want to meet him.
Sibar!
I'm introducing our new champion.
That's Baizanga.
Baizanga, contact Voltes Five so that we
can destroy this planet.
Baizanga...
I'm looking forward to meeting you.
You are all chosen to defend our planet
Earth from Bosanian invasion.
Are you ready to defend our planet?
Yes, sir!
Voltes Five team...
because of your extraordinary skills and
abilities...
and your personal destinies...
you are the last defense of this planet.
Should other defense plans fail...
we are counting on you.
Do you include the medical team?
All of us...
should aim to achieve the highest
standards of battle.
Anything less is not acceptable.
So today, prepare yourselves...
for we are going to implement a critical
test.
The Voltes Five team shall openly attack
the camp...
as though they are Bosanians.
And the Voltes Five team shall
counter-attack the camp...
as though they are real alien invaders.
We will be using live ammunitions.
Turn off safety protocols.
The Voltes Five team shall try this
drill...
and the Camping Falcon's strategy for
defense.
Are there any questions?
No safety protocols?
So if we get hit, game over?
No, sir.
Live ammunition...
Kaboom!
We're dead.
Team...
this drill will help us prepare
ourselves...
in case of an actual Bosanian attack.
That's why...
all of us...
should do our best.
Yes, sir.
We are ready.
Everyone...
prepare for live weapons drill.
To your stations.
Attention.
All crew will check the screening on the
tower.
Extra...
this is not just a simple drill.
And?
So you don't trust your training since we
were kids?
I don't have much training, sir.
Guys, we got this.
We already defeated the enemy,
right?
We already did this.
What does Mama always say?
Be brave.
Be strong.
You know what to do.
Let the battle begin.
Pattern Delta.
Attack commencing.
Watch out, guys.
Here and there.
Focus.
Alright, countermeasures.
Good job, all this team.
You think you can beat us?
Let's see what they're made of.
Launch Falcon Missiles.
Full spreads.
Sky heroes in.
This is where the unique energy I'm
talking about comes from, Prince Vesados.
General Draco.
Begin the attack.
Nice.
Who was the direct hit on your cap?
Not me.
Me.
Especially me.
If it wasn't one of us, who was it from?
Wait, wait.
Bosan energy signature confirmed.
The Bosanians are back.
Battle stations, everyone.
Aye, aye, sir.
CBF defense protocol activated.
Activated.
Tactical station reports ready.
Engineering station ready.
Medical and life support reports ready.
It's a beast fighter.
Team, get ready for the real battle.
Let's go.
Don't let him get close to the camp.
And don't give him a chance to retaliate.
Roger.
Richard, you have the control.
I'm flying back to EDF headquarters.
I'll speed Oscar.
Chief Kelly, once I'm out, raise your
shields.
Aye, aye, sir.
Claw, boomerang!
Bomber, missile!
Lander, missile!
Frigate, missiles!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Watch out, watch out!
Mark, rig left!
This guy is too much.
He's still standing.
It's like he wasn't hit.
You just didn't hit our missiles.
It's scary.
And he's not our enemy.
Commander Robinson, helicopter is clear
from base.
Activating shields.
I can't believe this.
No matter what the Volt is doing,
the beast fighter doesn't seem to be
affected.
Commander Robinson, what's going on?
Marianne, I can barely hear you.
I'm out of CBF.
Hello, Marianne?
Commander Robinson?
Hello?
Patch me to Captain Valcom.
Copy, sir.
Yes, Commander?
Has anyone seen Marianne?
She was trying to call me when the line
was cut.
I'm sure she's already warning her
children.
Sergeant Major?
Sir?
Marianne Armstrong, now.
Copy that, sir.
Master Chief, hurry up.
We need to reach the headquarters as fast
as we can.
Copy, Doc.
Security!
Back to CBF immediately!
Next alert!
Oh, my God!
What's going on?
All right!
Destroy everything that attacks us!
Protect Camp Atolcos!
Team, attack!
Evade and maneuver!
What?
Are we going to lose to him?
Leave it to me.
Bomber in!
We need to help the Baltis team.
I agree.
Chief, arm Hawk missiles.
On!
On my signal.
Engage, full attack!
Load!
Missiles away!
Finish him!
Next alert!
Doctor!
Tactical detects enemy approaching!
What on earth is that?
Oh, that's creepy.
What is it?
It's a skull.
A symbol of death.
A sign to intimidate.
Psych warfare.
It might be another beast fighter.
Whatever it is, hopefully he won't be able
to penetrate the barrier of Camp Big Pac.
Now the real fun begins.
Let's fight!
Oh, Pasugod!
This one is a beast!
Brace for impact!
You think you're strong?
Baltis, bazooka!
Yes, chief!
Dr. Armstrong?
Marianne, Marianne!
It's dangerous here.
Let's move!
Move!
Oh no, the barrier is activated.
We won't be able to enter.
Hmm.
What a pity.
We won't be able to return to their nest.
Because of that.
They also made a mess.
Why are you pitying such a lowly creature?
Call Dr. Smith.
We're outside.
Right.
Please, don't be stupid.
Not now.
Please!
Dr. Smith!
Hello, Dr. Smith!
Richard!
Hello!
General Drak.
Play this one.
Let's see if you can still escape.
Marianne!
Master Chief!
Master Chief, we need to get out of here!
Commander, look.
The game we're playing is still alive.
Do you want me to finish it?
No!
Wait a minute.
What is she doing?
This one is brave.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
This creature is crazy.
Ah!
She threw us.
You're crazy!
You're crazy.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah!
She has a strong body.
She has a strong duty to the forces of the
terrorists.
That's why she's brave.
She needs to be killed.
All this team, you need to kill that beast
fighter and proceed immediately to Camp
Big Falcon.
There's another alien entity threatening
the camp.
We need you back.
We need you back in CDF.
You have fallen into the trap of the
enemy.
You are under attack.
Your mother is hurt.
What?
My mother is hurt?
Brother, let's go back now.
How is my mother?
Is she critical?
We don't know.
She's outside the barrier and we can't
lift the barrier.
The CBF will be compromised.
We need you here.
Roger.
Wait.
Where's the enemy?
He's scared.
He's hiding.
Let's go back to the camp.
No, no, no.
He's just hiding.
We need to find him so he won't bother us
again.
But brother, what about my mother?
Brother, I'm just worried about my mother.
We need to find her.
Steve Bigbert is right, okay?
This is just part of the strategy of the
beast fighter.
It will come out.
We're far stronger than this beast
fighter.
Whatever his strategy is, we will defeat
him.
Let's follow him.
We need to go back to the camp now.
Has Marianne been rescued?
Oscar, I'm going to try my best to rescue
her.
I'm just waiting for the right opportunity
to get her.
CBF command, we found Dr. Armstrong.
Retrieving her now.
We're going to look for the beast fighter.
Brother, don't.
My mother needs us.
Let's go back to the camp.
But brother, I don't want to.
Let's go back to our mother.
No, little John.
We need to find the beast fighter.
Because if we don't destroy him now,
he will come back later.
But what about his mother?
Didn't she say that his right hand is not
strong?
Don't you care what he's wearing now?
Maybe he's wearing something else.
Let's vault out.
Agreed.
We're preparing to vault out.
Bigbert, little John, listen to me.
We can't vault out now.
Because if we split up, we won't be able
to secure the base.
Okay?
More lives could be at risk.
Our mission is to protect the whole world.
Huh?
Captain, sir, activate hologram
transmission.
Aye, sir.
Sir, incoming hologram transmission.
Dr. Smith, what's happening in the camp?
Our defense missiles are going to match
against the Skull Ship.
Jet fighters are all shut down.
CBF is in danger.
Our force field barriers are about to be
compromised.
I'll see if I can send more
reinforcements.
That would be a great help.
Go!
Captain, sir, email Global Statute Report.
Copy, sir.
How's her condition?
Doc, it looks like she has internal
injuries.
Marianne, can you hear me?
Yes, son.
Don't worry, everything will be okay.
They're on their way back to the base.
Okay?
It will be okay.
Doc, we have to hurry.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
You didn't tell me that our fight against
the Terra Air Force would be easy.
You're right, John Fred.
We prepared them too much.
Draco!
Doc!
Just keep doing what you're doing.
I'm happy watching you.
Doc!
Just share it.
Mrs. Armstrong?
No, don't get up yet.
Your condition is not yet stable.
Doc, what about my children?
Have they returned to the base?
Not yet.
They're still fighting until now.
Marianne, don't do that, please.
I can do it, Doc.
I can do it on my own.
Please let me go.
You can't do it yet.
You need to rest.
Please, please, please.
Marianne, listen.
No, you listen to me.
I have the authority to leave this medical
bay even if you don't agree with my
decision.
I will leave for my children's sake.
Central Station, concentrate our missiles
to the scout ship to distract them.
Yes, sir.
There's no clear shot of the beast
fighter.
Maybe it was hit by a bolt.
Shall we send a tug to fire, sir?
Then hold on to my command.
It's up to bolt 5 now.
It's up to them.
Ah!
We have to get out of here.
Lieutenant John, divert all power reserves
to thrusters now, please.
Working.
All power reserves to thrusters now.
Sir,
there's an aircraft flying towards the
beast fighter.
I thought you said we don't have pilots.
Then who's flying that?
Chief, contact the pilot now.
On all stars, CBF fighter craft MR5R,
this is Camp Big Falcon Command.
Please identify yourself.
This is Dr. Armstrong flying MR5R over.
I'm so sorry, Richard.
I have to do this for my sons.
I can't let them down.
Marianne, what are you doing?
What's going on, Richard?
What's going on, Marianne?
I'm so sorry I can't follow you now,
Richard.
But for all of us here, I have to help
bolt S5.
I have to take care of my children.
So please pray for us.
Come back here.
You'll regret what you're doing.
Too late, Oscar.
I can't let them down.
I can't leave them now.
You're still weak.
You can't do this.
Don't underestimate a mother like me,
Richard.
I can do something to save my children.
So please tell them that I love them so
much.
No matter what happens, don't let them
down.
Please tell them that.
Marianne, no!
That's a negative!
Computer, close transmission.
Sirs, please stop the communication.
Can we try to override the autopilot
system?
It won't override yet.
It has priority alpha access to all CVS
systems.
You can't stop her.
Big Bird!
Little John!
Ah!
Activate his chain!
No!
You can't be Falcon!
Vice Sanger is losing!
Volt is fine!
John Fry, I told you the fight won't last
long.
Look, there's a jet.
They sent help.
I see Little John.
Team, I'm afraid to tell you, but your mom
is flying that fighter jet.
What?
Your mom?
Are you sure your mom is flying that?
Let my sons go!
What's that?
Where did that come from?
your mom is flying that fighter jet.
Why did she allow her to fly?
She ran to the medical bed.
And before we knew it, she commanded one
of the fighter jets.
Mom is so annoying.
Brother, is there a way for us to talk to
her?
Nothing.
Call in through the command center,
Little Jim.
Dr. Smith, please.
Do everything you can to call your mom.
Give her a big falcon, please!
Team, I already did that, but your mom
won't listen.
Dr. Smith, please tell your mom that her
sons are begging here.
Go back to the camp right now!
Tell her that now!
Marianne, because I talked to your sons,
go back to the camp and I agree with them.
Go back to the camp now!
What are you attempting, Marianne?
Marianne, don't do it.
It's suicide.
Computer, open transmission.
My sons, I love you so much.
Mom, don't do this.
Mom!
Marianne, abort!
Abort!
Steve, Big Bert, Little John.
Mom!
Steve!
That's enough, Little John.
You'll cry later.
Now we need to be stronger.
Mom!
Let's have a match, Mama.
Big Bird, laser sword.
My son, don't let them win.
Wait for their punishment.
Mama!
Jules!
Are you saying something?
Natal Montesmay.
Sivay Sanger.
Jennifer...
Wait!
Don't speak!
Jules...
Have we made our new plan?
It's over, Prince Bessartos.
It's over.
Mama!
I'm sorry.
I feel sorry for the brothers.
It looks like they have lost hope,
sir.
Let's let them cry.
Let them cry like boys.
But I expect that when they stand up
again...
they will rise as warriors...
and avenge their mother and protect our
planet.
Rise, Armstrong brothers.
Rise!
I believe in the warmth of your eyes and
your pain.
Comrades of the Five.
Follow the survivor.
Put everything on the line.
Let's do it, until we run out of strength.
Everyone's smiles...
are magical.
I will not die...
until all the people of Bosnia and
Herzegovina are free.
I am Baron Rothgard.